bookinguz.com 2016-12-02

# Privacy policy

The main provisions of our privacy policy can be formulated as follows:

  * We do not share Your personal information with third parties.
  * We do not share Your contact information without Your consent.
  * You assign the volume of the disclosed personal information by yourselves

### The information collected:

We collect two types of information about You:

  * the first is the personal information You knowingly agreed to disclose to us by placing an order on the selection of the tour, or by subscribing to the distribution;
  * the second is technical information automatically collected by the Website software during the visit

The personal information is transmitted to us in several ways:

1\. Subscription to the distribution. To subscribe to our voluntary distribution and receive e-mail from us, you must provide us with your email address and name (real or fictional). This information is provided by you is voluntarily and its accuracy we have not verified.

2\. Technical information. During a visit by you a Website, the Website administration information automatically becomes available from standard logs, server logs). This includes the IP address of Your computer (or the proxy server, if it is used to access the Internet), the name of the Internet service provider, domain name, browser type and operating system, information about the website from which You made the transition to the Website, Website pages that You visit, the date and time of these visits, the files You download. This information is analyzed by us in the aggregate (impersonal) state to analyze Website traffic, and is used in the development of proposals for its improvement and development. The link between Your IP address and Your personal information is never disclosed to third parties, except in those cases where it is required by law.

### The use of information obtained

The information provided by you when you subscribe on a voluntary mailing list, going through third-party software Site and stored on the server. Access to this information has only the administrator of our account on this service. We use this information only to send You the information on which You subscribed. To unsubscribe from receiving mailings, You need to write a request letter in the mail [[info@bookinguz.com](mailto:info@bookinguz.com).](mailto:info@bookinguz.com.) This email address is being protected from spambots. You must have JavaScript enabled to view it.

### Providing information to third partiesе

We take very seriously the protection of your privacy. We never provide your personal information to third parties unless it is required by Uzbekistan legislation (for example, upon request of the court). All contact information that you provide to us, is disclosed only with your permission. Email addresses are never published on the Website and are used only for communication with you.

Data protection

The Website administration shall protect the information provided by the users, and uses it only in accordance with this privacy Policy. The Site uses conventional security methods to protect information from loss, tampering, and unauthorized distribution. Security is implemented by means of software firewall, access checking procedures, the use of cryptographic means of information protection, privacy policy.

Please do not use e-mail and instant messaging services such as ICQ to send passwords, because this method of communication may not provide the necessary data protection.

### The use of cookies

On the Website it is used the technology for user authentication, based on the use of cookies. Cookies are small files placed on your computer by a web browser.  
When the User is using the Website on the computer used for access, can be written cookies, which will later be used to automatically authenticate the User on the Website, and to gather statistical data about Website traffic. We never store personal data or passwords in cookies.

If You believe that, for whatever reasons, the use of cookies is unacceptable to You, You can prevent the saving of cookies on your computer used to access the Website by configuring the browser. It should be borne in mind that all the services that use this technology will be unavailable.

### Links to other sites

The Website may contain links to other websites. We, in turn, are not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. We encourage You to be aware when You leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each website that collects personally identifiable information about the user. This privacy policy apply solely to information collected by the Site [http://www.bookinguz.com](http://www.bookinguz.com/)

In order the hackers or other third parties have not gained access to your account, you must observe the following recommendations. Remember that all actions performed on the Website by the User authorized your account is deemed to be personally. The reverse burden of proof lies on you.

Do not use simple (for example, 12345) or too short passwords (up to 4 characters) and password with meaning (for example, your name, pet name or date of birth of family member). Ideally, the password should be a meaningless combination of letters and numbers. Never disclose Your password to any third party. Never leave your password in a conspicuous place (e.g., the "sticker" on the monitor).

If you suspect that your password may have become known to others, as soon as you can change it. Always finish the session on the Website under Your account, especially if you work on the computer to which you have access by others.

Never agree to keep the password for a site, if the web browser will prompt you to do this, if you are not working on your computer or a public access computer (for example, in Internet cafes, gaming club and so on).

Never check the box "Remember" if you’re not working on your computer or a public access computer. Always control who has access to your mailbox. Remember that using e-mail, the attacker can recover (change) the password and access your account.

Remember that the Site Administration will never ask You to send by e-mail or report otherwise Your password, just as we will never send or report otherwise forgotten Your password. The new password you decide on the password recovery page.

### Final regulations

Any statements contained herein do not constitute a contract or agreement between the Site Owner and the User providing personal information. The purpose of this document is to inform You about our approach to work with personal data.

We reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy. Notification of changes You get with a personal message on behalf of the Administration of the Website, or via e-mail to the address specified in Your account. Your continued use of the Website or its services after notice of changes has been sent to You, constitutes Your consent to the change.
